IBT0059
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Adminsitrative Files
1946-1986
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0059
19 Cubic Feet 19 record center cartons
- From Microfilming Process, 1946-1986; Series 1; 28.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  Records that were not properly captured during the microfilming process.
  - Microfilm Rolls 1670-1673, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1666-1669, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1664-1665, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1661-1662, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1660, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1645-1653, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1634-1643, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll #36, 1955-1961 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll #37, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll #38, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm Roll #39, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm Roll #40, 1949-1963 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm Roll #41, 1956-1961 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm Roll #42, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm Roll #43, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Microfilm Roll #44, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm #45, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Microfilm #46, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Microfilm #47, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Microfilm #48, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Microfilm #49, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Microfilm #50, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Microfilm #51, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Microfilm #52, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Microfilm #53, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Microfilm #54, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Microfilm #55, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Microfilm #56, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Microfilm #57, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Microfilm #58, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Microfilm #59, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Microfilm #60, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Microfilm #61, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Microfilm #62, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Microfilm #63, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Microfilm #64, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Microfilm #65, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Microfilm #66, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Microfilm #67, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Microfilm #68, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Microfilm #69, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Microfilm #70, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Microfilm #71, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Microfilm #72, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Microfilm #73, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Microfilm #74, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Microfilm #75, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Microfilm #76, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Microfilm #77, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Microfilm #78, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Microfilm #79, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Microfilm #80, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Microfilm #81, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Microfilm #82, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Microfilm #83, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Microfilm #84, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Microfilm #85, 1956-1962 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Microfilm #86, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Microfilm #87, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Microfilm #88, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Microfilm #89, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Microfilm #90, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Microfilm #91, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Microfilm #92, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Microfilm #93, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Microfilm #94, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Microfilm #95, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Microfilm #96, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Microfilm #97, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Microfilm #98, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1674-1675, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1676-1677, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1678, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1684-1689, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1697-1698, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1700-1704, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1705-1714, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1716-1721, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1723-1759, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1763-1779, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1780-1786, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1788-1793, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1795-1796, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1801-1807, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1808-1810, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1811, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1812, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1813, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1813, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1813, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1814, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1814, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1815, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1815, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1815, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1816, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1816, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1817, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1817, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1818, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1819, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1820-1846, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1847-1852, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1853-1857, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1858-1861, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1962-1863, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1864, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1865-1867, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1868-1869, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1870, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1870, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1870, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1871, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1871, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1872-1873, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1874, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1875, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1876, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1876, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1979, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1878, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1877, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1877, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Rolls 960-969, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Rolls 970-979, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1000-1090, 1926-1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1090-1099, 1944-1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1100-1117, 1962-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1118-1120, 1958-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1121-1129, 1958-1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1130-1159, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1160-1182, 1962-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1241-1451, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1452-1467, 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1468-1471, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1472-1499, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1507-1528, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1545-1567, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1568-1585, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1586-1598, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1599-1604, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1608-1621, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Rolls 1622-1623, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll #112, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll #137, 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll #147, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll #142, 1935-1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll #143, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll #144, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll #145, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll #135, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll #136, 1942-1952 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll #138, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll #139, 1942-1948 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll #140, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll #141, 1943-1959 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll #125, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll #126, 1944-1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll #127, 1945-1954 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll #128, 1953-1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll #129, 1948-1959 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll #130, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll #131, 1952-1959 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll #121, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll #122, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll #110, 1938-1959 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll #123, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll #124, 1943-1958 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll #111, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll #112, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll #108, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll #109, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll #104, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll #105, 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll #106, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll #107, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll #99, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll #100, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll #101, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll #102, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll #103, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm Roll 2968-2980, 1969-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 2981-3015, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 3016-3050, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 3051-3124, 1932-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 3126-3147, 1948-1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 3148, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 3158-3164, 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 3164-3168, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 3208-3342, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 3342-3343, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 4182-4234, 1922-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 4235-4454, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 4455-4499, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 4500-4569, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 4570-4584, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 4585-4599, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 4600-4649, 1979-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 3171, 1969-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 4650-4671, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 148, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 149, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 150, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 151, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 152, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 153, 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 154, 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 155, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 156, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 157, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 158, 1953-1958 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 159, 1951-1958 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 160, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 167, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 169, 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 169, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 170, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 172, 1953-1959 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 174, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 175, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 177, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 179, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 183, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 184, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 186, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 187, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 189, 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Mirofilm Roll 190, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 191, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 195, 1953-1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 199, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 201, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 168, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 202, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 203, 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 204, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll 205, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll 347, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 348, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 349, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 350, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 351, 1942-1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 352, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 353, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 354, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 355, 1954-1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 356, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 357, 1956-1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 358, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 359, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 361, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 363, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 364, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 365, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 369, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 370, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 371, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 372, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 374, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 375, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 375, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 389, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 377, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 378, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 380, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 381, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 390, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 397, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 398, 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 399, 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 400, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 406, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 407, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll 418, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll 411, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm Roll 419, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm Roll 420, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm Roll 421, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm Roll 422, 1957-1965 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm Roll 423, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Microfilm Roll 424, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm Roll 425, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Microfilm Roll 426, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Microfilm Roll 427, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Microfilm Roll 429, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Microfilm Roll 430, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Microfilm Roll 437, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Microfilm Roll 438, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Microfilm Roll 439, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Microfilm Roll 440, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Microfilm Roll 442, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Microfilm Roll 443, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Microfilm Roll 446, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Microfilm Roll 1, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 2, 1949-1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 3, 1953-1957 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 4, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 5, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 6, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 7, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 8, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 9, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 10, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 11, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 12, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 13, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 14, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 15, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 16, 1953-1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 17, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 18, 1953-1959 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 19, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 20, 1955-1959 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 21, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 22, 1955-1959 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 23, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 24, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 25, 1953-1959 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 26, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 27, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 28, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 29, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 30, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 31, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 32, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 33, 1953-1958 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 32, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 34, 1955-1959 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 36, 1955-1959 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll 1908, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 1909, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 1908, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 1908, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 1907, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 1906, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 1911, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 1911, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 1910, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 1909, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 1913, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 1912, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 1912, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 1911, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 1915, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 1914, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 1913, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 1913, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 1917, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 1916, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 1916, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 1915, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 1922, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 1921, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 1920, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 1919, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 1918, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 1918, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 1924, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 1923, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 1923, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 1923, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 1929-1939, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 1925, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 1924, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm 1880, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm 1881, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm 1882, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm 1882, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm 1883, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm 1884, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm 1885, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm 1886, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm 1886, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm 1887, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm 1888, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm 1888, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm 1889, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm 1890, 1968-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm 1891, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm 1892, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm 1893, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm 1894, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm 1895, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm 1896, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm 1896, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm 1897, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm 1898, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm 1899, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm 1900, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm 1901, 1963-1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm 1901, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm 1902, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm 1903, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm 1904, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm 1905, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm 2354-2361, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm 2362-2399, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm 2400-2416, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm 2417-2447, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm 2448-2469, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm 2470-2476, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm 2477-2484, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm 2485-2488, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm 2489-2491, 1973-1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm 2492-2503, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm 2504-2520, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm 2521-2524, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm 2525-2529, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm 2530-2532, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm 2533-2539, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm 2540, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm 2541, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm 2542, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm 2546, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm 2541, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm 2543-2545, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm 2547-2549, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm 2549, 2550, 2551, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm 2554, 2553, 2552, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm 2553-2556, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm 2557-2558, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm 2559, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm 2559-2566, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm 2567-2569, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm 2128, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm 2129, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm 2130, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm 2132, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm 2133, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm 2134, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm 2136, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm 2137, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm 2138, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm AG60, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm 2139, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm 2140, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm 2141, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm 2142, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm 2144, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm 2145, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm 2146, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm 2149, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm 2150, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm AG-68, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm 2151, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm 2154, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm 2155, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm 2155, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm 2154, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm 2155, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm 2156, 1968-1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm 2159, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm 2162-2199, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)